# Nguyen Thanh Phong

#### Coder

Phone 0912227910
Birthday 1999/08/10

Email Phongb1706853@gmail.com

Address Ninh Kieu, Can Tho city



## **Summary**

I am a final year student preparing to graduate. I hope to get a stable job to devote my abilities and learn more experiences to improve myself. I always calmly find solutions to difficult problems. I won't give up until the job is done. I will improve my skills to get the job done, whether it's a new job, a new technology or even a new language.

## **Work Experience**

2020/09 - 2020/12

#### **Built A Website Application By Dotnet Core (C#)**

- The application achieves full functionality as designed.
- · The application runs on multiple platforms.

2020/07 - 2020/10

#### **Built A Mobile Application By Flutter (Dart)**

- · The application is very smooth.
- The application can install on mobile phone.

2020/02 - 2020/05

#### **Built A Desktop Application By Java**

- The application is complete and achieves basic functions such as design.
- Pass the test of the instructor.

#### **Education**

2017/8 - Present

#### **Can Tho University**

Final year students majoring in Information Technology.

- GPA out of 4: 3.2
- · Full time

#### **Skills**

**Fluently C# -** My best skills is C# consist: ASP.NET MVC Framwork – Core, Entity Framwork, Window Form, WPF.

Database management - Has worked with Microsoft SQL server and MySQL server.

Basic language - Can built website by HTML, CSS and javascript.

Object oriented programming- Master of object oriented programming (C# and Java)

English skills - Listen, speak and especially fluently read professional document.



# **Project**

# Junk food post management website

(2020/09 - 2020/12)

Instructor	Master Le Van Quan
Project description	The website that manages the posts of the junk food stores. It also allows register for accounts
	to post, as well as confirm orders from consumers. Source code is managed on Azure in Visual
	Studio 2019 so that team members can work independently of each other.
Number of members	5
Position	Team Leader
Role in project	Together with members to analyze and design database for website.
	Select Teamplate for website.
	Research how to work and manage source code on Azure.
	Build module homepage, post, post details.
	Support members to solve the problem, as well as fix bugs.
Technologies used	Frontend: HTML, CSS, Jquery, JavaScript
	Backend: ASP DOTNET Core MVC, Microsoft SQL Server, Azure.

## Car rental mobile application with Flutter

(2020/07 - 2020/10)

Instructor	Doctor Tran Hoang Viet
Project description	The application allows to book a car online. Allows users to register to rent a car with all the
	basic functions of a car rental application on mobile.
Number of members	1
Position	Coder
Role in project	Database design analysis.
	Research flutter technology of Google.
	Build application with databases managed on MySQL.
	Connect application with database on webhost via API.
	Store source code on GitHub.
Technologies used	Flutter (Dart language of Google).
	MySQL Server.
	Web API of 000WebHost.com
	• Git

# Desktop application for managing cafes

(2020/02 - 2020/05)

Instructor	Master Vu Duy Linh
<b>Project description</b>	The application allows to order drinks on the spot, pay, manage bills and manage drinks.
Number of members	3
Position	Coder
Role in project	Analyze and design database.
	Build moduel payments, book a table and manage bills.
	Database management of the application with MySQL.
	Connect the database to the application.
Technologies used	Java and MySQL server.